B.
Kitty and her classmates are talking about unusual schools in different countries.
Work in groups and share your opinions on this topic.
Use the conversation below as a model.
Do you know any unusual schools around the world?
Yes, I know about the boat school in Bangladesh.
During the rainy season there's much more rain in Bangladesh than in many other parts of the world.
Thanks to the boat school, children have a chance to learn even when there are floods.
What a good way to get the children learning!
Another example is the bottle school.
People in the Philippines and Guatemala build this kind of school with used plastic bottles.
This is very cheap and good for the environment.
That's really cool!